<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--$Revision: 1.4.4.1 $  $Date: 2004/04/01 16:12:54 $-->
<!--Copyright 2003 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<demos>
	<name>Link for ModelSim</name>  
	<type>toolbox</type> 
	<icon>$toolbox/matlab/icons/matlabicon.gif</icon>    

<description>

&lt;p&gt;The Link for ModelSim(R) integrates MathWorks tools into the Electronic Design Automation 
(EDA) tool flow by providing a communication interface between Model Technology's HDL Simulator, 
ModelSim, and The MathWorks products MATLAB and Simulink. Link for ModelSim enables hardware 
designers and system integrators to efficiently create, design, validate,
and verify hardware designs with an integrated tools environment. The integrated
environment enables designers to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;* Easily create test signals and test benches to verify algorithms&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Validate models against reference designs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Translate legacy HDL descriptions into system-level views&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Test Benching with MATLAB&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link for ModleSim provides an interface
for validating and visualizing ModelSim VHDL models within the MATLAB environment.
To apply the interface, you need to code a VHDL model and an M-function such
that they can share data. Once you complete the coding, you link the applications and start a 
test benching session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link for ModelSim offers flexibility
in how you start and control a test benching session.
A session can consist of a single MATLAB function invocation, a series of timed invocations,
or invocations based on timing data returned by an M-function to ModelSim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link for ModelSim MATLAB demos include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;* Random Number Generator&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Manchester Receiver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Oscillator&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Manchester Receiver can also be used as a tutorial. This demo tests three components 
of a VHDL Manchester receiver. After each of the first two components is tested, press any key to 
trigger the test for the next component.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Cosimulating with Simulink&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, ModelSim, Simulink, and Simulink blocksets provide a powerful 
modeling and cosimulation environment for EDA. 
ModelSim Cosimulation blocks link hardware components that are concurrently simulating in ModelSim to 
the rest of a Simulink model. One usage scenario is a single ModelSim Cosimulation block that 
fits into the framework of a larger system-oriented Simulink model.  Another scenario is a Simulink 
model that is a collection of ModelSim Cosimulation blocks, each representing a specific hardware
component.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link for ModelSim Simulink demos include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;* Manchester Receiver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Manchester Receiver using Communication Blockset&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Manchester Receiver using multiple VHDL Cosimulation blocks&lt;/p&gt;

</description> 

    <demosection>
	<label>Link for ModelSim MATLAB demos</label>
    	<demoitem>
		<label>Random Number Generator</label>
		<callback>modsimrand</callback>
	</demoitem>
      <demoitem>
      	<label>Manchester Receiver</label>
		<file>html/manchesterreceiverdemo.html</file>
     		<callback>manchestertutorial</callback>
      </demoitem>
	<demoitem>
      	<label>Oscillator</label>
		<callback>modsimosc</callback>
      </demoitem>

    </demosection>

    <demosection>
       <label>Link for ModelSim Simulink Demos</label>
       <demoitem>          
		<label>Manchester Receiver</label> 
		<callback>manchestermodel</callback>
       </demoitem>
       <demoitem> 
        	<label>Manchester Receiver using Communication Blockset</label>
         	<callback>manchestermodelcommblks</callback>
      </demoitem>
	<demoitem> 
        	<label>Manchester Receiver using multiple VHDL Cosimulation blocks</label>
         	<callback>multimanchester</callback>
      </demoitem>
    <demoitem> 
        	<label>Manchester Receiver using mixed design(Verilog and VHDL)</label>
         	<callback>mixedmanchester</callback>
      </demoitem>
    </demosection>

</demos>

